Kayden Potter

678 Address Road, Newark, NJ k.potte r @ myema i Loom (125) 456-7890

Energetic and committed inside sales representative with more than six years of experience. Adept at conducting client consultations and interpreting their needs to present the most effective solutions to their problems. Well-versed in managing the sales process from prospecting to closing and building loyalty to secure repeat custom.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Business Management (Marketing)

Martin Tuchman School Of Management, New Jersey Institute Of Technology, Newark, Nj, September 2010-June 2014

Key Skills

- Engaging and professional sales style
- Adept at building Lasting client relationships
- Clear and concise written and verbal communicator
- Lead generation
- Product demonstration

Professional Experience

Inside Sales Representative

Evolus, Newark, NJ I March 2017 - Present

- Organize and deliver events and customer education programs promoting a range of natural beauty products to drive revenue and consistently exceed sales quotas
- Build quick rapport with customers and create a positive impression of the brand, keeping in regular contact to establish Long-term loyalty
- Maintain up-to-date knowledge of the features, benefits, and clinical data for all products and communicate information clearly to clients
- Analyze sales data regularly, noting emerging trends and identifying areas for growth and improvement

Inside Sales Representative

Cornerstone onDemand, Newark, NJ | July 2014- March 2017

- Sourced and followed up on new leads via telephone and email
- Listened closely to clients' needs to gain deep insights into their business models and challenges and suggest effective solutions
- Negotiated terms of service and generated Legal contracts
- Demonstrated products and services to current and potential clients online and in-person and provided ongoing support